Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/2
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Retirement Pension Plan For Agents In District Offices, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: Let's Get Acquainted, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: A Career in Life Insurance, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 4: it happens all the time, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 5: Opportunities in sales and service In John Hancock Group Insurance And Group Pensions, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 6: Marketing Management Opportunities, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 7: Summer Management Training Program at John Hancock, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 8: Marketing In The Space Age, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 9: Careers In Operations Research & Management, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 10: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
    July 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Careers In Management, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 12: Actuarial Development Program, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Contract, Publication (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: History of Life Insurance And Of The John Hancock, Publication (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Item 2: John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance, Publication (Box 28, Folder 43)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Decisions Issued In Two Arbitration Cases, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 2: Company Suspension For Leading Walkout Upheld, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 3: Accord Reached For Contract, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 4: Contact: A District Agency Communication On Labor-Management Developments, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    July 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: First Week Of Negotiations Draws Near Close, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    June 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Strike Called As Union Bargaining Committee Rejects Company Proposals, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 7: Contact: A District Agency Communication On Labor-Management Developments, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    July 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: New Debit Accounting Program Moves Ahead, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 9: Contact: A District Agency Communication On Labor-Management Developments, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    June 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: New Debit Accounting System Ready For Field, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 11: New Accounting System Near Demise, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 12: Contact Wishes A Happy Holiday Season To All Its Readers, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 13: Need Seen To Accelerate MDO Debit Growth, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 14: Demands Exchanged At Newark Negotiations Set For June 6 In Capitol, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 15: Three-Year Contract Negotiated Ratifcation Solid, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 16: Negotiations Approach Deadline, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    June 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Contract Negotiations Recess, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 18: Negotiations Move Through First Week, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    June 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Two-Year Contract Agreement Reached, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Item 20: Contract Negotiations Recessed, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    June 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Contract Negotiations Underway, Publication (Box 28, Folder 44)
    June 4. Item is in English.
- Box: 29, folder: 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Johns-Manville annual report 1973, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Johns-Manvilleyour future?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Johns-Manvilleyour future?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: 94th Anniversary Johns-Manville Corporation 1952 Annual Report TO Stockholders, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    January 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: 93rd Anniversary Johns-Manville Corporation 1951 Annual Report To Stockholders, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    January 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: 96th Anniversary Johns-Manville Corporation 1954 Annual Report To Stockholders, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    January 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Facts And Figures About Canadian Johns-Manville Company, LTD., Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Item is in English; French.
  - Item 8: 1946 Annual Report To The Employees of Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    March 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Season's Greetings Editorial Staff, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Meeting the J-M Family Tree, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Fountains of New York, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: J-M In National Defense, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: A Happy Holiday, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Future, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Summer Employee Educational Assistance Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Look at Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Working Together in Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Application Forms, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: "Payment of Tuition", Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Careers In Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Manua l of Standard Practices, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Manual of Standard Practices, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    September 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Induction Into The Company, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Working Together in Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: careers Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: If You Want To Save, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Voluntary Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    June 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Saving For The Future, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Group Life Insurance Protection, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Group Major Medical Protection, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Hospitalization Surgical And Medical Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Payment of Tuition, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    July 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Hospitalization, Surgical And Medical Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Group Life Insurance In Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Saving For The Future J-M Retirment Plan in U.S., Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Abestos Strike, Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
    May 11. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 2: Compulsory Unionism? A Statement by Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Gazette, Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Asbestos Strike, Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Compulsory Unionism? A Statement by Johns-Manville, Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Johns-Manville A condensed description of the company's background and its present organization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Johns-Manville is in your Future, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Johns-Manville's New Research And Development Center, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Johns-Manville's New Research And Development Center, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Johnson & Johnson Bulletin annual report to employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Annual Report To Employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Johnson & Johnson Bulletin Annual Report to Employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: What Do You Suggest?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: New Look at the World, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: What Do You Suggest, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: 1965 Johnson & Johnson Annual Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Retirment Plan of Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Your Group Insurance, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Salaried Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Monthly Investment Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: How Much Do You Really Earn?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Careers In Manufacturing And Distribution Services At Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Johnson & Johnson Personnel Department Activities, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Careers In Engineering And Maintnenace At Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Careers In Finance And Accounting At Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Your Job With Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Careers, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Testing Programs, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Sales & Distribution Services, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Personnel Department Services And Coverage, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: you and Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: you and Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between Johnson & Johnson Ethicon Suture Laboratories, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America of the C.I.O., Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Johnson Family of Products, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: 78 Years of Progress A History of Johnson & Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: How to Light a Candle, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Robert W. Johnson. November. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Our Management Philsosophy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Executive Development, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Earl G. Planty. November 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Johnson's Mutual Benefit Association Constitution And By-Laws, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: this company of ours, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: A Story of Growth, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
    By Howard M. Packard. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Story of Growth, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Business Week, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: The Johnson Weekly, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
    July 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Johnson Magazine New Look at the World, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Johnson Magazine History Underfoot, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Employee Opinion Survey, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Your Ideas Are Worth Money, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: The Johnson Foundation Annual Report 1958, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Welcome to the home of Johsnon's Wax, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: Handy Household Waxing Guide, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: this company of ours, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Exit Interview Guide, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Employee's Personal Record Of Earnings and Benefits, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Opportunities with Johnson's Wax, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Employment Application, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Opportunities with Johnson's Wax, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: This company of ours, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Application For Sales Position, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Opportunities with Johnson's Wax, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Income And Benefits In Your Retirement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Employee Benefits At Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The Johnson Foundation Scholarship Program For Sons And Daughters Of Employees Of S.C. Johnson & Son, Inc., Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Employee Benefits At Johnson, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: The Johnson Foundation 1955 Annual Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Major Medical Expense Benefits, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Johnson Mutual Benefit Association Constitution And By-Laws, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Income and Benefits in Your Retirement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Employee Benefits At Johsnon/s Wax, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Educational Aid TO Employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: Income And Benefits In Your Retirement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: The Johnson Foundation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Johnson wax Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: History - Johnson Wax Retiree Bus Trips, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Get Ready For A Bang-UP Trip, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    August 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: It's Picnic Time For All Johnson Retirees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    June 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: JMBA, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    May 20-21. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Peter Cottontail Invites All Johnson Wax Retirees/Widows To Hop Along The Bunny Trail, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    April 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Sure Hope You Can Join Us For The Fun, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
    March 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Johnson Old Timers' Events Review, Publication (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Your Ideas Are Worth Money, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Your Ideas Are Woth Money, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Your Ideas Are Woth Money, Publication (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Johnson Magazine, Publication (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Jonwax Journal, Publication (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Johnson's Wax Alumni Album, Publication (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: School Systems Report On Using The American Economy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: The United States Economy In Action, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Publications, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Materials For The Teacher, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Materials for the Teacher, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Team, Publication (Box 29, Folder 23)
    February 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Team, Publication (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Manual Covering the Administration of the Basic Accident Prevention Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: "J&L" The Growth of An American Business, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: In The United States District Court For The Northern District Of Alabama Southern Division Consent Decree I, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: General Safety Guides For All Employes Safety is Everybody's Business, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Pension Agreement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Savings and Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Program of Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: Attention Files Information Office, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
    November 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Career Opportunities with Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: JalTEAM Almanac, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
    May-June. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: JalTeam Almanac, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Item 14: Suggestion Plan For Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation And Subsidiary Companies, Publication (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Kaiser Foundation Health Plan, Inc., Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Addendum To Group Medical And Hospital Service Agreement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Addendum To Group Medical And Hospital Service Agreement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Addendum To Group Medical And Hospital Service Agreement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Kaiser Foundation Medical Care Program 1965, Publication (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
    September 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bigger and Better, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Savings & Retirement Plan For Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Shop Rules and Regulations Kaiser-Frazer Corporation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Your Opportunity With Kaiser Aluminum, Publication (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Kaman Performance, Publication (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Kaman Performance, Publication (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: 1962 Annual Report For Employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Highlights of a good year, Publication (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Kansas Public Employees Retirement Act, Publication (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Employees' Information Manual, Publication (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Kansas Public Employees Retirement Act, Publication (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Faculty Handbook Kansas State University, Publication (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Information Pamphlet For Classified Employees, Publication (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: faculty handbook, Publication (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Box: 29, folder: (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Box: 30, folder: 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Relations Between Management And Employes, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Questions and Answers on The Relations Between Managtement and Employees at Kaufman's, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The Relations Between Management and Employes, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution And By-Laws Of The Graphic Arts Independent Union, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Think..Act..Get Cash Awards, Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: KIM, Publication (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Supervisors Guide Kemper Insurance Policy And Procedure For Employees With A Drinking Problem, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 1963 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Protection, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
    December 21. Item is in English.
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Department Weekly Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    May 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Supervisors' Newsletter, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    May 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Supervisors' Newsletter, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    March 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Kennevadan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The Kennezonian, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Supervisors' Weekly News, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    March 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Chino Newsletter, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: A Suggestion could easily Hit Pay Dirt, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Kennecott Copper Corporation Annual Report 1963, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Kennevadan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Kennecott Copper Corporation Annual Report 1958, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Good Ideas Are Worth Money, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: A Suggestion could easily Hit Pay Dirt, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Kennecott Copper Corporation Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Kennescope, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Utah Copper Story, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: All About Kennecott The Story of Kennecott Copper Corporation, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Utah Copper Story, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Utah Copper Story, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: All About Kennecott The Story Of Kennecott Copper Corporation, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Copper Mining In Ray and Hayden Arizona Yesterday and Today, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: This Is Chino, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Kennecott Research Center, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: How Kennecott Got Its Name, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Chinorama, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
    November-December. Item is in English.
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 10)